Y'all see Nicki Minaj on there with that man who got murked with his wife?
This administration is full of people with heart and soul.
Now, I know many will look at that and simply attribute it to her performing for personal
reasons, attributed to, you know, charges against her brother, against her husband.
However, there is a greater geopolitical implication that is being missed.
And if you don't know about Trinidad, if you don't know how Trinidad is connected to Venezuela,
et cetera, you would be missing it.
Yeah.
So I'm actually going to break that down for y'all, but you're going to have to subscribe
to my Patreon.
It's $5.
So I'm going to break that down for y'all.
What time is it?
So at eight o'clock, I'm going to break down that situation for you because a lot of folks
are overlooking a very major factor as to what's going on there.
And I think I've got it.
So see you at my Patreon.
Link in bio.
Tooddly links.
Support a real one.